

Moses C Nwigberi

Web and iOS dev

About Me

Dedicated and detail-oriented entry level web developer for 4 years with 2+ years of professional experience. Eager to apply modern web technologies and skills in creating, maintaining, and completing client mobile and web software application demands. Special interest in creating things that live on the web.

Professional Experience

ZZDIGITAL studios. 2020-present. Web developer

Key responsibilities:

- created and updated the frontend/ui of existing websites.
- updated ui for clients webpages.
- worked with junior web developer and design teams totally revamping dovehospital.com, a renowned health organization
- Consulted with the management team to develop long-term solutions to client requests.
- Designed email templates for an iOS software backend
- · Satisfactorily created multiple functional static websites on request.

ZZDIGITAL studios 2020-2021. iOS developer

Key responsibilities:

- Learned Swift.
- · created a few iOS applications.
- collaborated with the design team and senior iOS developer developing the front end of a Yacht ordering mobile app.

2018-present.

- · Learned HTML, CSS, JQuery
- Perfected JavaScript (2020)
- learned JavaScript frameworks.
- Currently prefers and develops with NextJs

My Contact

mosesnwigberi@gmail.com

(+234-807-548-9362

Ocoperative villas estate, badore

https://themoeportfolio.vercel.app

Hard SkillS

- · Responsive web development
- HTML, CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- JQUERY
- BOOTSTRAP
- REACT
- NEXTJS
- SVELTE/SVELTEKIT
- GI
- SWIFT/XCODE
- NOSQL DATABASES.

Soft Skill

- Observation
- Time management
- Communication
- Multi-tasking

Education

EBSU STAFF SECONDARY SCHOOL
SSCE

Completed in 2017

 University of Lagos, Akoka Bachelor of Engineering

on going